Guide to the Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, 1995-2006.
Rawlings, Hunter Ripley papers, 1995-2006
- Series II. Papers
  - Atlantic Philanthropies, September 13, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 72)
  - General Motors Visit, September 25-26, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 73)
  - EPE Celebration Dinner, September 26, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 74)
  - Student and Academic Services, September 27, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 75)
  - Dr David A. Cofrin and David H. Cofrin, September 27, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 76)
  - Exemplary Alumni Service Awards, September 27, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 77)
  - Cornell Entrepreneur of 2002 Reception Dinner, September 26, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 78)
  - Tri-Institutional Faculty Procedures, September 11, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 79)
  - HRR Schedule Updates, July 22, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 80)
  - Lunch with Richard Cliggott, September 24, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 81)
  - Driving Directions, September 24, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 82)
  - Dinner with Greenwich/Westchester Alumni, September 24, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 83)
  - Board of Directors, August 21, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 84)
  - HRR Itinerary for NYC and Connecticut, September 23-25, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 85)
  - Academic Cabinet Meeting, September 23, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 86)
  - AAU Executive Committee, September 17, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 87)
  - AAP Advisory Council, August 20, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 88)
  - David W Butler, September 4, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 89)
  - College of Engineering's Fall Faculty Reception, September 19, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 90)
  - Recruiting Notebook, September 18, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 91)
  - Aramark (Box 122, Folder 92)
  - Alumni Affairs and Development, August 12, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 93)
  - Overseers' Retreat, October 1, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 94)
  - Peter Szilagyi, September 19, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 95)
  - NCAA, December 3, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 96)
  - COFHE Section 568 Presidents Working Group and other Records, December 14, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 97)
  - COFHE 568, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 97A)
  - Capital Funding and Priorities Committee, November 19, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 98)
  - Montpellier, October 29, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 99)
  - Hillary Clinton, August 7, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 100)
  - SCAN, July-November 2003 (Box 122, Folder 101)
  - Committee on Board Membership, September 23, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 102)
  - Shirley Cunningham (Box 122, Folder 103)
  - Miscellaneous Meetings, October 2002 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Bates College Inauguration, October 26, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Events, October 2002 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - ILR Correspondence, October 2002 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, September-October 2002 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - AAU Meetings, October 20-23, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Dinner with Washington DC Alumni, October 22, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Academic Deans, September 23, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8A)
  - Strategic Planning- Finance, September 15, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8B)
  - VP Facilities and Construction Strategic Plan, September 13, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8C)
  - Strategic Planning Advisory Board, September 12, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8D)
  - Strategic Planning- Miscellaneous Background Papers, May-August 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8E)
  - Strategic Planning Advisory Board, August 24, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 8F)
  - Strategic Planning Miscellaneous Correspondence, July-September 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8G)
  - Strategic Planning, March 15, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8H)
  - Strategic Planning, May 3, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 8I)
  - Strategic Planning, May 1994 (Box 123, Folder 8J-8K)
  - Executive Team '90 RB, February 26, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Provost-General, April 29, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - JGSM Strategic Plan, September 23, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11A)
  - A and LS Strategic Plan, September 20, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11B)
  - Engineering Strategic Plan, September 20, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11C)
  - ILR Strategic Plan, September 23, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11D)
  - Human Ecology Strategic Plan, September 27, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11E)
  - Grad. and Prof. Strategic Planning Task Force, November 9, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11F)
  - Information Technologies Strategic Plan, September 27, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11G)
  - Public Affairs Strategic Plan, September 27, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11H)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, April 1995 (Box 123, Folder 12A)
  - Strategic Planning Advisory Board, November 15, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12B)
  - Signature, October 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12C)
  - Strategic Planning Advisory Board, October 10, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12D)
  - Biological Sciences Strategic Plan, October 10, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12E)
  - Student and Academic Services Strategic Plan, October 10, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12F)
  - Hotel Strategic Plan, October 4, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12G)
  - AA and P Strategic Planning, September 22, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12H)
  - Law School Strategic Plan, September 21, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12I)
  - Veterinary Medicine Strategic Plan, September 20, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12J)
  - Arts and Sciences Strategic Plan, September 19, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12K)
  - Downs '69 Forum Flap, April 6, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Faculty Commission on H.E. Report, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 2A)
  - Faculty Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box 124, Folder 2B)
  - Faculty Senate, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 3A)
  - Faculty Senate, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 3B)
  - Faculty Senate OPUF, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 3C)
  - Faculty Senate Affirmative Action Committee, August 6, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - New Faculty Orientation, September 28, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Emeritus Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 6A)
  - Provost's Statement on Transition to Emeritus Status, December 10, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 6B)
  - College Emeritus Faculty Policies, February 16, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 6C)
  - University of Chicago Retirement Papers, December 22, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 6D)
  - Faculty Salaries, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 7A)
  - Faculty Salaries, October 21, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 7B)
  - Financial Policies Committee, December 14, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 7C)
  - Faculty Trustee Task Force on Long Range Financial Planning, November 22, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 7D)
  - Intercollege Compensation, March 7, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 7E)
  - Salary and Statistics, October 29, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 7F)
  - Retirement General, June 12, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Transition of Faculty to Emeritus, June 17, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 9A)
  - Faculty Retirement Miscellaneous, May 8, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 9B)
  - Kaminsky, July 29, 2003 (Box 124, Folder 10A-10B)
  - Unionization Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 11A-11B)
  - Unionization Council/Legal Related, 2007 (Box 124, Folder 12A)
  - Unionization Sunny Powers, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12B)
  - Unionization Board of Trustees, October 25, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12C)
  - Unionization Conference Calls, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12D)
  - Unionization University of Pennsylvania's Recognition, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12E)
  - Unionization Temple University's Recognition, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12F)
  - Unionization Cornell's Position (Box 124, Folder 12G)
  - Unionization Ronald Ehrenberg Paper, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12H)
  - University of Pennsylvania/NLRB November 2002 Decision, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 12I)
  - Unionization Miscellaneous, May 31, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 13A)
  - Unionization Articles, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 13B)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 124, Folder 14A)
  - Responses to Housing, October 9, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 14B)
  - Residential Communities, October 1997 (Box 125, Folder 1A)
  - Residential Communities, April 1996 (Box 125, Folder 1B)
  - Residential Communities, 1995 (Box 125, Folder 1C)
  - Academic Program Review, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Residential Communities Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 3A-3F)
  - Program Houses (Res. Communities), 1995-1996 (Box 125, Folder 4A)
  - Program Houses (Res. Communities), 1995-1996 (Box 125, Folder 4B)
  - Res. Community Reports, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - CU Housing Study, 1997 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000 (Box 126, Folder 1A)
  - John Niland Visit, May 3-7, 2001 (Box 126, Folder 1B)
  - Coalition Meeting with New York Times, October 7, 1998 (Box 126, Folder 2A)
  - ETH (Swiss MIT), May 2000 (Box 126, Folder 2B)
  - Kyoto Now, February 2001 (Box 126, Folder 3A)
  - HRR Statement on Civil Discourses, May 1, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 3B)
  - HRR Statement on Affirmative Action, April 10, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 3C)
  - Streett Report on 1993 Day Hall Takeover, February 16, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 3D)
  - Rhodes Statement on Hispanic Unrest, October 30, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 3E)
  - Rhodes Statement on Gay/Lesbian/Bisexual Living Unit, April 22, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 3F)
  - WGD Statement on Cornell Public Safety Procedures, April 7, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 3G)
  - Incidents-Photo Policy, June 8, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 3H)
  - Procedures for Disruptive Events, March 26, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 3I)
  - Revised Draft on Campus Disorders, August 12, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 3J)
  - FR Statement on Anti-Racism Coalition’s Demands, April 17, 1986 (Box 126, Folder 4A)
  - FR Statement on Campus Mood, September 24, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 4B)
  - FR Statement on Human Relations, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 4C)
  - Barker Statement on Racial/Sexual Harassment, January 20, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 4D)
  - FR Statement to University Community, June 10, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 4E)
  - FR Notes on South Africa Issue Statement, September 26, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 4F)
  - FR Letters to Campus and Sun (South Africa), April 26, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 4G)
  - FR Open Letter to Cornell Community, April 7, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 4H)
  - Barcello Report, March 31, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 4I)
  - ACA CAB - Data, April 1998 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Biological Science Program Review, December 1998 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Biological Science Program Review, September 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3A)
  - Biological Science General, September 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3B)
  - Biological Science Final, November 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3C)
  - Presidential Consultants on the Biological Sciences, 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3D)
  - Biological Sciences Web-Cooke, October 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3E)
  - Task Force Report, March 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3F)
  - Biological Sciences External Consultants, September 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3G)
  - Biological Sciences Responses, September 1998 (Box 127, Folder 3H)
  - Asia, January 2002 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Life Sciences External Advisory Committee, November 2001 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - AAU Business, January 2003 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Department of Asian Studies, May 2005 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - AAU Draft Statement, December 2002 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997 - 2006 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - SUNY, October 1995 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Open Meetings Law, 1989-1995 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Coalition, 1998 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Coalition, 1998 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Call to Engagement, 2003 (Box 127, Folder 14-15)
  - Ward Center for Nuclear Sciences, 2001 (Box 127, Folder 16-22)
  - Genomics Initiative, 1999 (Box 127, Folder 23-24)
  - Ivy League, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Ivy Manual, 2001-2002 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Ivy League Athletic Background Material, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Ivy League, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 4-7)
  - Ivy League, 2002 (Box 128, Folder 8-12)
  - Ivy League, 2003 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Judicial Administration Search, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Judicial Administration Candidate-Barbara Krause, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Barbara Krause Reappointment, 1997 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Judicial Administration Search, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Bugliari Committee, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - Freedom of Speech, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Judicial Administration-Proceedings for Appointment, 1973-1977 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Judicial Administration-Search, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - Judicial Administration-Advising Committee, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Judicial Administration Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - Bugliari, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - Michael Egan, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 25)
  - Policy Statements, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 26)
  - Association of Emeritus Professors, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 28)
  - Division of Alumni Affairs, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 29)
  - Photo Policy, 1972-1978 (Box 128, Folder 30)
  - Photo Policy, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 31)
  - Memorials and Named Facilities, 1983-1984 (Box 128, Folder 32)
  - Vice President for University Relations, 2003 (Box 128, Folder 33)
  - Logo-Letter Head, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 34)
  - University Relations Annual Reports, 2001 (Box 128, Folder 35)
  - Cayuga Festival-Barbara Mink, 2004 (Box 128, Folder 36)
  - Vice President for Government and Community Relations Search, 2003 (Box 128, Folder 37)
  - Possible Cornell Columbia Medical Colleges Merger, 1995-1999 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - New York Hospital Space, March 1996 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Bill Gates, 1999 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Weiss Presidential Fellows, 1999 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Berlin Conference Papers, October 12, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Academic Exchanges and Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - AD White Professors At-Large, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Turin Agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Humboldt Agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2001 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 2001 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Einaudi/Center for the Environment, July 1, 2002 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - KyotoNow, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- Series III. Interim President Papers (June 2005-July 2006)
  - Hilary Clinton, Save America's Treasures Grant, October 2005 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Ad Hoc Faculty Committee, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - SUNY Alfred, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Diversity, February 17, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Hurricane Katrina Relief Files, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Speeches
    - Haverford College Board, 2006 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - National Academy Foundation, 2006 (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
    - National Humanities Center, 2005-2006 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Workforce Planning Quotation, July 2005 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Rawling's Web Welcome, July 2005 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - West Campus Quotation, July 2005 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Atacama Project, July 13, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Seneca Place Ribbon Cutting, July 26, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Diversity Conference, July 30, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report Introduction, 2004-2005 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Tolani Family Dinner, August 5, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Physics TA Workshop, August 19, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - New Student Convocation, August 20, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Meeting Notes, August 25, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Cornell on the Commons, August 27, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Sage Chapel Opening Service, August 28, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Presidential Councillors, September 12, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - China Achebe Introduction, September 15, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Community Leaders Brunch, September 17, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Multi-Sport Visit, September 17, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Hans Bethe, September 18, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Materials Science and Engineering Anniversary, September 20, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Miller Dinner, September 20, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Major Gifts Committee, September 21, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Arts and Sciences Advisory Committee, September 22, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Constitution Day, September 23, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Leadership Alliance Greeting, September 23, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Law School Advisory Council, September 23, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Homecoming Away from Home, September 24, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - United Way Pre-Mailing, September 26, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Engineering Fall Faculty, September 26, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 32)
    - Johnson and Johnson, October 3, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 33)
    - Employee Address, October 4, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 34)
    - West Campus Kramnick, October 6, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 35)
    - United Way Kick-off, October 6, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 36)
    - Michael Zak Professorship, October 12, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 37)
    - Bauer Hall Dedication, October 14, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 38)
    - Murphy Lobby Dedication, October 14, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 39)
    - Weiss/Lynch Visit, October 15, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 40)
    - Life Sciences Advisory Board, October 19, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 41)
    - Undergraduate Business Program Campaign Celebration, October 20, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 42)
    - State of the University Address, October 21, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 43-44)
    - Cornell Fund Breakfast, October 22, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 45)
    - Malcolm Bilson Banquet, October 23, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 46)
    - Op-ed Science Advocacy, October 2005 (Box 130, Folder 47)
    - Bronfenbrenner Memorial, October 2005 (Box 130, Folder 48)
    - Hunter and Elizabeth Rawlings Holiday Greetings, October 2005 (Box 130, Folder 49)
    - Entrepreneur of the Year - Robert Toll, November 2, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 50)
    - Faculty Programs, November 2, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 51)
    - Robert Baker Professorship Dedication, November 3, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 52)
    - 400 Club Breakfast, November 9, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 53)
    - Black Classicists, November 10, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 54)
    - Weiss Presidential Fellows Lunch, November 10, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 55)
    - Katrina Relief, November 11, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 56)
    - China and Asia-Pacific Studies (CAPS) Signing and Dinner, November 15, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 57)
    - Beijing Forum, November 16, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 58)
    - Tsinghua Conference, November 17, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 59)
    - Shanghai Cornell Club, November 17, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 60)
    - Hong Kong All Alumni, November 18, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 61)
    - CAPS Dinner hosted by Robert and Pauline Kuok, November 19, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 62)
    - China Background, November 2005 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - John S. Dyson Professorship, November 29, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Philanthropies Reception, December 13, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Genomics Fellows Reception, December 15, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - January Graduate Reception, December 18, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Major Gifts Committee, January 18, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Weill PhD Students Town Meeting, January 18, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - President's Circle, January 18, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Student Phonathon, January 23, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Mosaic Conference Briefing/Taping, January 23, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Rotary, February 1, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Senior Class Campaign Kick-Off, February 7, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Lindseth Lunch, February 7, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Temple Grandin Introduction, February 15, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Chinese Consolate Lunch, February 16, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Harris Dinner, February 20, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Investment Committee, February 24, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - McGovern Dinner, February 24, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Sheila Johnson Toast, March 2, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Hilary Clinton Visit, March 3, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - United Way Celebration, March 7, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Silicon Valley Advisors, March 28, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Central Carolina All Alumni, March 24, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Las Vegas Alumni Interest Group, March 25, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Cornell Silicon Valley, March 28, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - CALS Advisory Committee, March 31, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - PCCW University Update, March 31, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - IPEI Event, April 3, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Marilynne Robinson, April 5, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 29)
    - Greenberg Imaging Suite Dedication, April 11, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 30)
    - Cornell-China Lecture, April 13, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 31)
    - Hatfield Lecture: R. Tata, April 16, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 32)
    - New York City Tower Club, April 18, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 33)
    - Metropolitan Development Association (MDA), April 20, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 34)
    - Kaplan Family, April 22, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 35)
    - W. LaFeber Last Lecture, April 25, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 36)
    - Kanders Family Dinner, April 26, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 37)
    - Tanner Prize, April 26, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 38)
    - Library Council, May 1, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 39)
    - Los Angeles Tower Club, May 7, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 40)
    - Distinguished Faculty, May 15, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 41)
    - Staff Graduate Reception, May 17, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 42)
    - Weill Commencement, May 18, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 43)
    - Washington Tower Club, May 20, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 44)
    - Trustee Handbook - Skorton Bio, May 22, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 45)
    - McGovern Fields Dedication, May 24, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 46)
    - Merrill Scholars, May 24, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 47)
    - Senior Class Reception, May 26, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 48)
    - Newly Tenured Teaching Awards, May 27, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 49)
    - PhD Ceremony, May 27, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 50)
    - Commencement, May 28, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 51)
    - Larry Fuller - Foremost Benefactor, June 1, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 52)
    - Hans Bethe Symposium, June 2, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 53)
    - Samuel Fleming - Foremost Benefactor, June 4, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 54)
    - Service Awards, June 6, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 55)
    - Teagle Working Group Dinner, June 7, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 56)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1931, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 57)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1945, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 58)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1956 Panel, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 59)
    - Reunion 2006 - Oldest Class Reception '31, '36, '41, '46, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 60)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1966 (Breakfast), June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 61)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1961 (Dinner), June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 62)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1976, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 63)
    - Olin Lecture, June 9, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 64)
    - State of the University, June 10, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 65)
    - Cornell Black Alumni Association (CBAA) Reunion, June 10, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 66)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1951, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 67)
    - Reunion 2006 - Class of 1956, June 2006 (Box 131, Folder 68)
- Series IV. Media
  Includes Videos, DVDs, CDs and one Film Reel
  - "Cirque de Cornell" Celebrating the Inauguration of Hunter R. Rawlings III as tenth President of Cornell University., 1995-10-12; V-370
    Two copies
  - The Inauguration of Hunter R. Rawlings III as President of Cornell University., 1995-10-12; V-371
  - The Inauguration of Hunter R. Rawlings III as President of Cornell University., 1995; 688
    Use copy of V-371
  - Cornell University Inauguration of Hunter Ripley Rawlings III as president, October 12, 1995; V-821 (Box 105)
  - History and Humane Values in American Life, Hunter Rawlings, October 11, 1995; V-822 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Inauguration Installation Ceremony, October 12, 1995; V-823 (Box 105)
  - Asia Symposium, January 4, 2000; V-978 (Box 105)
  - Asia Symposium, January 6, 2000; V-979 (Box 105)
  - The Campaign for Undergraduate Education at Stanford, 2001; V-980 (Box 105)
  - Campaign Kickoff, Barton Hall, Frank Rhodes, Alma Mater, October 19, 1990; V-981 (Box 105)
  - CCE Weeks Highlights, October 1996; V-982 (Box 105)
  - A Chance to Participate, V-983 (Box 105)